is we're going to have to automate faster.
I don't know if this automation can happen
quickly enough. The meat facilities are
right now running under capacity.
Beef is up about 24%, depending on which
article you read. Much of it is due, you
can say, because of packer control, but
also because of the human hands that touch
our meat in the facilities. Can we
automate fast enough? To do so, I believe
that we're going to see more ag innovation
come from outside agriculture. What if the
new innovation is beyond just giving an
engineer a task and they change it 10%,
but instead they change it 100%?
Innovation will come to this industry from
outside, and we need to embrace it, not
reject it. Because innovation that comes
to agriculture might be from a completely
different 180-degree position, and you'll
say, like, holy crap, I can't believe we
didn't do that. Uber and Lyft were not
founded by the CEO of Yellow Cab, were
they? And I'm telling you what, I'm
opposed to it. When I was a kid at
Northwest Elementary School, I remember
the day that the policeman came in there
in kindergarten. The first thing he said
was, "Children, don't ever get into a car
with strangers." Now it's a business.
Think about that. You were told from the
time you were a kid, "Don't get in a car
with a stranger." Now it's just to hop in
a car when somebody pulls up and says,
"Are you Damon?" No. They can't get your
name right, and I hop in a car with them.
Makes no sense to me.
Thank you.
[music]